And now you're supposed to say,
"Wow, what an interesting fact.
(Leonard:)Come here, you crazy, nerdy guy.
I could never be mad at you."
(Penny:)Wow. That's all you got after you were
the most obnoxious person...
(Penny:)...on a double date
that included Howard Wolowitz?
(Leonard:)No, I'm sorry. I really am.
(Leonard:)It's not right
to mock what a person believes in.
(Sheldon:)Thank you.
You willing to go to my psychic
and see what it's about?
You willing to read a book...
(Leonard:)...that concisely explains
how all psychics are frauds?
(Penny:)I would not.
(Leonard:)-Okay, let's go see your psychic.
-Really?
(Leonard:)Well, yeah.
One of us has to keep an open mind.
(Penny:)-Saying I don't have an open mind?
-No. Let me help you with this stuff.
(Penny:)You know, I believe in ghosts too.
(Raj:)-Great.
-And astrology.
(Leonard:)I know.
And pyramid power and healing crystals.